<resources>
    <string name="app_name">GlirtProject</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>


    <string name="radio1">Very much like me</string>
    <string name="radio2">Mostly like me</string>
    <string name="radio3">Somewhat like me</string>
    <string name="radio4">Not much like me </string>
    <string name="radio5">Not like me at all</string>

    <string name="title1">1.I have overcome setbacks to conquer an important challenge</string>
    <string name="title2">2. New ideas and projects sometimes distract me from previous ones. </string>
    <string name="title3">3.My interests change from year to year.* </string>
    <string name="title4">4. Setbacks don’t discourage me. </string>
    <string name="title5">5. I have been obsessed with a certain idea or project for a short time but later lost interest.* </string>
    <string name="title6">6. I am a hard worker. </string>
    <string name="title7">7. I often set a goal but later choose to pursue a different one.* </string>
    <string name="title8">8. I have difficulty maintaining my focus on projects that take more than a few months to complete.</string>
    <string name="title9">9. I finish whatever I begin.</string>
    <string name="title10">10.I have achieved a goal that took years of work. </string>
    <string name="title11">11.I become interested in new pursuits every few months.*</string>
    <string name="title12">12.I am diligent. </string>

    <string name="shareResult"> "HI! I got my grit score from this app"It define my passion and perseverance for long-term goals.
        Share among your friends. Download it at https://www.sumanastani.com.np/blog and know yout Grit as well</string>
    <string name="title_activity_tab">TabActivity</string>
    <string name="section_format">Hello World from section: %1$d</string>

    <string-array name="gritInformation">
        <item>a combination of passion and perseverance for a singularly important goal—is the hallmark of high achievers in every domain.</item>
        <item> Grit offers a truly sane perspective: that true success comes when we devote ourselves to endeavors that give us joy and purpose.”</item>
        <item>Grit is the tendency to sustain interest in and effort toward very long-term goals (Duckworth et al., 2007)</item>
        <item>Grit is passion and perseverance for long-term goals.</item>
        <item>Talent and luck matter to success. But talent and luck are no guarantee of grit. And in the very long run, I think grit may matter as least as much, if not more.</item>
        <item></item>
    </string-array>

</resources>
